benton williams

social and digital media specialist

profile

"Hey, I'm Benton Williams. I'm a 17-year-old high school student from Cartersville, Georgia who loves to create. I've been exploring my passions in photography and digital content production for the past several years, and I have been using my experience as a digital native to help local businesses cultivate an online presence through social media strategy and website design."

experience

social and digital media specialist

cartersville farmers market, apr 2020-present

- Analysing social media statistics to create effective and engaging content
- Capturing high-quality photos using a DSLR camera and editing in Lightroom to be used for social posts and publications
- Collaborating alongside vendors and city officials alike to innovate creative strategies to enrich ourcommunity
- Conceptualising and coordinating social media campaigns both paid and organic
- Developed consistent social media strategies to promote the market, educate on the importance of eating/supporting local, and cultivate relationships between consumers and local producers
- Established and oversees connections between the market and external services used to enhance vendor experience

north cobb christian school

marketing intern, aug 2021-present

- Enhancing the school's online presence with DSLR photography and videography for social media
- Drafting press releases and other external communications for news outlets around metro atlanta
- Producing all-school events such as graduation, chapels, and the annual Circle of Prayer
- Revitalising brand identity by writing and designing practical style guidelines for internal and external usage

contact

hey@bntn.io 678.882.2341 bntn.io @heyimbenton

education

high school diploma north cobb christian school 2012–2023

expertise

- photography
- content creation
- digital design
- communication
- pragmatism
- networking

skills

- instagram
- twitter
- adobe creative suite
- later
- slack & discord
- notion
- github

certification

adobe lightroom skill assessment linkedin